<resources>
    <string name="app_name">One-Fit-All</string>

    //Spotify playlists options
    <string name="spinner_prompt">Choose a playlist</string>
    <string-array name="playlists">
        <item>Choose a playlist</item>
        <item>Workout – 120 BPM</item>
        <item>Born To Run 150 BPM</item>
        <item>160 BPM Running Pop</item>
        <item>Run \'N\' Bass 170 – 175 BPM</item>
        <item>180 bpm born to run</item>

    </string-array>

    //workout card titles
    <string name="createWorkoutCard"> Create Workout </string>
    <string name="supportCreateWC"> Have a recurring workout? Add it here!
        By using the View Workouts feature you can save those amazing workouts for future GAINS!!!
        Or try the Quick Workout feature. Add some quick gains to your amazing day with the countdown timer.</string>
    <string name="viewWorkouts"> View Workouts </string>
    <string name="viewDescription">Found a new workout? Try saving it here at the View Workout page.
        Record the muscle group, type of exercise, sets, and more! And remember the GRIND DOES NOT STOP!!!</string>
    <string name="quickWorkout"> Quick Workout </string>
    <string name="quickDescription"> Enter the amount of sets you desire to do, the amount of time
    you want to GRIND for, and finally the amount of time you want to rest for. Enjoy your workout!!!</string>
    //calorie burner titles
    <string name="calorieBurnerCard"> Calorie Burner </string>
    <string name="supportCalorieBC"> Want to know how many Calories you burned? Use the Calorie Burner!
        Record how many calories you have burned during your workout and make sure to update the amount
        after each workout to track of your progress. #Gains</string>
    <string name="calorieBurner"> Update Calories </string>
    <string name="burnerDescription"> Met Level is the intensity of a workout. The harder you work the
        higher the level (scale 1-16). Make sure to enter the Duration in minutes and your weight in kilograms.</string>
    <string name="intakeParagraph"> Wondering how many calories that yummy snack has? Try looking it up
        either using the search bar or scanning the barcode. Do not be shy, look it up.</string>
    //calorie counter titles
    <string name="calorieCounterCard"> Calorie Counter </string>
    <string name="supportCalorieCC"> Try the Calorie Counter to look up different food items for
        their caloric information. And while you are at it record how many calories you
        consumed so far! Finally make sure to keep track of your progress. #FoodisYummy</string>


    //bottom menu nav
    <string name="bm_home">Home</string>
    <string name="bm_workout">Workout</string>
    <string name="bm_journal">Journal</string>
    <string name="bm_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="userInch">User Inch</string>
    <string name="userFt">User Ft</string>
    <string name="Update">update</string>
    <string name="View_Data">viewData</string>
</resources>